Register of the Stefan Jędrychowski papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Photographs, 1941-1989
  - Large photographs, 1944-1988
    - 1973 (Box 4)
      Speaking at anniversary marking 170 years of insurance products in Poland on 1973 May 24; in a May Day parade; COMECON ceremony in Karl-Marx Stadt on 1973 October 18.
    - 1974 (Box 4)
      At COMECON meeting in Kórnik, Poland; signing COMECON protocol in Ulan Bator on 1974 October 14; other official functions as Minister of Finance.
    - 1976 (Box 4)
      In Budapest on 1976 July 21.
    - 1977 (Box 4)
      Touring a factory in Székesfehérvár, Hungary on 1977 July 20.
    - 1981 (Box 4)
      Begin interviewed.
    - 1988 (Box 4)
      Gathering of former members of the Krajowa Rada Narodowa on 1988 December 29.
    - No date, miscellaneous (Box 4)
      Visit to Uniwersytetu Mikołaja Kopernika w Toruniu; Spotkanie komitetem organizacyjnym; „Odznaczenia budowniczych mostu” Szczecin?, with Gomułka, Cyrankiewicz and others.
  - Oversize photographs, 1960-1976 (Box 5)
    Multiple photographs pasted to a large exhibit-worthy sheet showing optical equipment on exhibit in Warsaw in 1960 early May; mounted, exhibit-worthy handwritten record of civil engineering and industrial development accomplishments in Łodż since 1950, dated in blue ink 1963 November 3; visit to steelworks Italsider-Taranto in 1966 June; receiving award from Soviet Ambassador Aristow, 1967 November 6; meeting with Janos Kadar and t. Łukaszewicz, 1976 July 28.